<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kali&#39;s Posts on Kaalikutty</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kali&#39;s Posts on Kaalikutty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 12:05:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19</title>
      <link>/posts/covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:45:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covid-19/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 4 months, Its been 4months, living my life Scared of you... You wiped out many lives from this world You pulled down many lives in this world Every call from my parents makes me nervous Every day thinking about you, that one day you will grab me too with your hands Many beautiful lives give up without even saying a bye to their loved ones. They give up without even seeing their kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Lead Me to You the Silent Patient</title>
      <link>/posts/silentpatientpart-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:37:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/silentpatientpart-1/</guid>
      <description>Started my reading taste with Novoneel Chakraborty&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;The Stranger Trilogy&amp;rdquo;.
There were days which I have taken off from my work and spend those days to finish the book series. Addicted! Heartbroken! Excited!Thrilled! &amp;hellip;. a lot of mixed feelings. It took many weeks to recover from the hangover of reading such a long series. Lots of work to do, lots of things to do at home, eventually I stopped reading other books of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Alcestis choose not to speak when she was back alive?</title>
      <link>/posts/silentpatientpart-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:37:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/silentpatientpart-2/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any idea even after reading about Alcestis. What could be the reason when a woman decided to be silent? Many !.Because a woman is a mystery. She remains silent for many reasons. She might be destroyed inside or she might be waiting to explode or she might be&amp;hellip;..who can explain. Nobody!
She surrenders her life to her husband. She was an ideal of how women love her husband.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>